careerlink.org 2018-01-24

# Job Search, Career Advice & Employer Tools | Careerlink

## AIM Online Privacy Statement

AIM is an innovative not for profit that grows, connects and inspires the tech talent ecosystem through career development and educational programs. Through these efforts, we improve thousands of lives in the Silicon Prairie. 

## Collection of Your Personal Information

In order to access some AIM services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password, which we refer to as your credentials.  At some AIM sites, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number.  We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.  If you choose to make a purchase or sign up for a paid subscription service, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address that is used to create an AIM billing account.  We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with AIM sites and services.  We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.  In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with AIM, information collected through one AIM service may be combined with information obtained through other AIM services. 

## Use of Your Personal Information

AIM collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested.  These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.  We also use your personal information to communicate with you.  We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements.  We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from AIM and its affiliates.  Sharing of Your Personal Information Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of AIM and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent.  Some AIM services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company.  If you register for or use such services, both AIM and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.  We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on AIM; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of AIM (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AIM services or members of the public. 

## Resumes And Resume Databases

AIM allows you to post your resume in our database.  This feature allows you to market yourself to potential employers.  When you post your resume in our resume database, then all businesses subscribing to our services will have access to your name, resume and contact information.  We use our best efforts to grant access to this database only to subscribing businesses, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not, without our consent, gain access to this database.  You may remove your resume from our search-able database at any time.  However, businesses subscribing to AIM services may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases.  We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes in these instances, or for the use or privacy of resumes by any of such parties for resumes submitted to our database.  By using your selected ID and password, you may, at any time log in to the resume feature to, inactivate, change or correct your resume from the resume database or inactivate, change or correct your name and contact information. 

## Online Applications Hosted by AIM

Information you submit in response to a specific job posting is considered "personal information" and will be retained in our database.  We use logins and passwords to protect this information.  The information may also be provided in computer readable form directly to the respective employer for retention within system(s) that are solely under the control of that employer.  We believe the employers represented on this site consider any resumes they receive to be valuable and worthy of appropriate protection; however, we cannot control how the application information provided to employers is used, stored, protected or distributed. 

## Online Applications Not Hosted by AIM

Some employers request AIM to direct applicants to an online application hosted by the employer or by a third party.  AIM will attempt to provide notification when a visitor is leaving an AIM Web site.  AIM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  You should review the privacy policies of any other Web site. 

## Communication Preferences

You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from AIM sites and services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.  These communication choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain AIM services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service. 

## Security of Your Personal Information

AIM is committed to protecting the security of your personal information.  We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.  For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities.  When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.  If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.  Do not share this information with anyone.  If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

## Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information

Many AIM sites and services are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children.  When an AIM site does collect age information, and users identify themselves as under 13, the site will either block such users from providing personal information, or will seek to obtain consent from parents for the collection, use and sharing of their children's personal information.  We will not knowingly ask children under the age of 13 to provide more information than is reasonably necessary to provide our services.  We encourage you to talk with your children about communicating with strangers and disclosing personal information online. 

## Use of Third Party Ad Networks

The majority of the online banner advertisements you see on AIM Web pages are displayed by AIM.  However, we allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on AIM Web pages.  Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement.  In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on.  This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.  AIM does not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.  AIM maintains a relationship with a third-party currently operating as Salary.com.  Salary.com might maintain relationships with a number of third-party ad servers or ad networks.  Those ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting.  You may find more information at the Web site of either the individual ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

## Remarketing

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Careerlink website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. 

Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).

## Links to Other Sites

This site may contain links to other sites.  AIM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  You should review the privacy policies of any other Web site. 

## Controlling "Spam" or Unsolicited E-mail

AIM is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial e-mail, or "spam." AIM will not sell, lease or rent its e-mail subscriber lists to third parties. 

## Enforcement of This Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact [privacy@aimforbrilliance.org](mailto:privacy@aimforbrilliance.org). 

## Changes to This Privacy Statement

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback.  When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement.  If there are material changes to this statement or in how AIM will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification.  We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how AIM is protecting your information. 

## Contacting Us

AIM welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement.  If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact [privacy@aimforbrilliance.org](mailto:privacy@aimforbrilliance.org). 

Last Updated: August 2, 2016
